TERRY HUNT JR.

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

(813) 810-4515

thunt4jr@gmail.com

terryhunt.dev

SKILLS

- Fluent in American Sign Language
- ReactJS/NodeJS
- JavaScript
- HTML/CSS
- Front End Coding
- Database Administrator
- SEO/SEM
- Newsletters Systems
- eCommerce Management
- Figma
- Google Cloud
- AWS
- Azure
- Netlify
- Heroku
- Bootstrap/React-Bootstrap/Reactstrap
- Tailwind CSS
- Material UI

PROFILE

Detail-oriented HTML, and CSS developer with 10+ years of experience developing, testing, debugging, and maintaining WordPress. Constantly motivated to stay up to date with technologies such as JavaScript, React, Sainity.io, Strapi, headless CMS, Nodejs, and Express.

EXPERIENCE

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Freelance

2021 - Present

- Learning JavaScript, NodeJS, ReactJS, and Express.
- Database administration and website design.
- Create blogs and eCommerce using Strapi and Sanity.
- Consulting clients on improving online presence for their businesses. This includes appearance, grammar, speed performance, backup system, and uptime.

WEB DEVELOPER/OWNER

Whoa Website, LLC

2013 - 2020

- Provided shared hosting on a self-managed dedicated server for WordPress/WooCommerce, Prestashop, and various CMS with over 200 clients per server with 99.999% uptime.
- Helped triple clients' sales by revamping their front-end, marketing, and SEO websites.
- Increased client's sales by nearly 60% between \$300,000 \$2 million per year.
- Designed and launched 60 websites per year.
- Maintained over 20 eCommerce websites per month, including products, SEO, and newsletters.
- Worked with MailChimp, Sendy, SendinBlue, and WordPress
 Newsletter plugin achieved 96% successful rate with deliveries.

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF APPLIED SCIENCE

Technology Development & Management Software Development

President's Honor List

St. Petersburg College

2020 - 2021

ASSOCIATE OF ARTS

General Studies

St. Petersburg College

2019 - 2020

ASSOCIATE OF SCIENCE

Software Application Development

High Honor Roll List

Rasmussen College

2015 - 2017

SOFTWARE APPLICATION DEV CERTIFICATE

Rasmussen College

2017

VOLUNTEER

Reefmaker

2018- Present

Shadow Lakes Homeowners Association

2020 - Present

Grand Concourse Railroad

2022 - Present

Suncoast Animal League

2021 - 2022

New Life Dog Rescue

2014 - 2021

ProjectDEAF

2016 - 2021

PRESIDENT (VOLUNTEER)

ProjectDEAF - It's a Deaf Thing - Deaf Expo

2016-2021

- Managed 72 volunteers during the day of the events
- Responsible for promoting the events on social media marketing
- Increased newsletter system from 300 to 6,000 subscribers
- Ranked #1 against competitors on Google & Yahoo
- 2018 Fundraisers exceeded the organization's goal by over \$10,000
- Deaf Expo was sold out with over 4,000 attendees attending the event
- Designed and managed the websites for ProjectDEAF and It's a
 Deaf Thing Deaf Expo

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR

Westgate Baptist Church

2012 - 2014

- Built a new library, including 13 new desktops for high school students under the budget of \$10,000 using TechSoup
- Improved the CCTV, card access reader maglock system, and security system
- Reduced the expense of \$800 per month for ISP/Cable/VoIP to \$300 per month by switching to Verizon
- Managed website for the church
- Responsible for the entire network and servers onsite and cloudbased

INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY STAFF

Orbital Corporation - Temporary

2012 - 2012

- Improved Company's network with new CAT5 cables and network station.
- Repaired all desktops
- · Built and managed the website
- Updated 60,000 records in the database during the contract time frame.
- Helped the assembly line on manufacturing military hardware for the US Navy